<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!--
   Cards Against Humanity black card list, from the first expansion.

   Derived from work copyright by Cards Against Humanity LLC,
   Licensed under Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 2.0
   Generic (CC BY-NC-SA 2.0)
-->
<deck name="1stexp">
<card>An international tribunal has found <blank /> guilty of <blank />.</card>
<card>My plan for world domination begins with <blank />.</card>
<card>And I would have gotten away with it, too, if it hadn't been for <blank />!</card>
<card>Michael Bay's new three-hour action epic pits <blank /> against <blank />.</card>
<card>What has been making life difficult at the nudist colony?</card>
<card>In a pinch, <blank /> can be a suitable substitute for <blank />.</card>
<card>In the distant future, historians will agree that <blank /> marked the beginning of America's decline.</card>
<card>When I pooped, what came out of my butt?</card>
<card>Next season on Man vs. Wild, Bear Grylls must survive in the depths of the Amazon with only <blank /> and his wits.</card>
<card>In its new tourism campaign, Detroit proudly proclaims that it has finally eliminated <blank />.</card>
<card>The CIA now interrogates enemy agents by repeatedly subjecting them to <blank />.</card>
<card>I learned the hard way that you can't cheer up a grieving friend with <blank />.</card>
<card>What brought the orgy to a grinding halt?</card>
<card>In his new self-produced album, Kanye West raps over the sounds of <blank />.</card>
<card>What's the gift that keeps on giving?</card>
<card>When all else fails, I can always masturbate to <blank />.</card>
<card>Science will never explain <blank />.</card>
<card>In Rome, there are whisperings that the Vatican has a secret room devoted to <blank />.</card>
<card>Dear Sir or Madam,<br />We regret to inform you that the Office of <blank /> has denied your request for <blank />.</card>
<card>The socialist governments of Scandinavia have declared that access to <blank /> is a basic human right.</card>
</deck>
