<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!--
   Cards Against Humanity black card list, from second expansion.

   Derived from work copyright by Cards Against Humanity LLC,
   Licensed under Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 2.0
   Generic (CC BY-NC-SA 2.0)
-->
<deck name="2ndexp" woeid="23424977">
<card>In his newest and most difficult stunt, David Blaine must escape from <blank />.</card>
<card>Little Miss Muffet Sat on a tuffet, Eating her curds and <blank />.</card>
<card>This month's Cosmo: &ldquo;Spice up your sex life by bringing <blank /> into the bedroom.&rdquo;</card>
<card>You haven't truly lived until you've experienced <blank /> and <blank /> at the same time.</card>
<card woeid="2459115">Members of New York's social elite are paying thousands of dollars just to experience <blank />.</card>
<card>Tonight on 20/20: What you don't know about <blank /> could kill you.</card>
<card>I went from <blank /> to <blank />, all thanks to <blank />.</card>
<card>Before <blank />, all we had was <blank />.</card>
<card>Charades was ruined for me forever when my mom had to act out <blank />.</card>
<card>The votes are in, and the new high school mascot is <blank />.</card>
<card>My mom freaked out when she looked at my browser history and found <blank />.com/<blank />.</card>
<card>The healing process began when I joined a support group for victims of <blank />.</card>
<card>The Five Stages of Grief: denial, anger, bargaining, <blank />, acceptance.</card>
<card>During his midlife crisis, my dad got really into <blank />.</card>
<card>If God didn't want us to enjoy <blank />, he wouldn't have given us <blank />.</card>
<card>After months of debate, the Occupy Wall Street General Assembly could only agree on &ldquo;More <blank />!&rdquo;</card>
<card>My country, 'tis of thee, sweet land of <blank />.</card>
<card>Everyone down on the ground! We don't want to hurt anyone. We're just here for <blank />.</card>
<card>This is your captain speaking. Fasten your seatbelts and prepare for <blank />.</card>
<card><blank /> would be woefully incomplete without <blank />.</card>
<card>My new favorite porn star is Joey &ldquo;<blank />&rdquo; McGee.</card>
<card>Before I run for president, I must destroy all evidence of my involvement with <blank />.</card>
<card>Only two things in life are certain: death and <blank />.</card>
<card>Next time on Dr. Phil: How to talk to your child about <blank />.</card>
<card>I spent my whole life working toward <blank />, only to have it ruined by <blank />.</card>
</deck>
