<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!--
   Cards Against Humanity black card list, from the third expansion.

   Derived from work copyright by Cards Against Humanity LLC,
   Licensed under Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 2.0
   Generic (CC BY-NC-SA 2.0)
-->
<deck name="3rdexp" woeid="23424977" version="1.0">
<card>Hey baby, come back to my place and I'll show you <blank />.</card>
<card>Lovin' you is easy 'cause you're <blank />.</card>
<card>After months of practice with <blank />, I think I'm finally ready for <blank />.</card>
<card>My life is ruled by a vicious cycle of <blank /> and <blank />.</card>
<card>Money can't buy me love, but it can buy me <blank />.</card>
<card>And what did <em>you</em> bring for show and tell?</card>
<card>Call the law offices of Goldstein &amp; Goldstein, because no one should have to tolerate <blank /> in the workplace.</card>
<card>Having problems with <blank />? Try <blank />!</card>
<card>I'm not like the rest of you. I'm too rich and busy for <blank />.</card>
<card>With enough time and pressure, <blank /> will turn into <blank />.</card>
<card>To prepare for his upcoming role, Daniel Day-Lewis immersed himself in the world of <blank />.</card>
<card><blank />: hours of fun. Easy to use. Perfect for <blank />!</card>
<card>Finally! A service that delivers <blank /> right to your door.</card>
<card>A successful job interview begins with a firm handshake and ends with <blank />.</card>
<card>During high school, I never really fit in until I found <blank /> club.</card>
<card>What left this stain on my couch?</card>
<card>As part of his contract, Prince won't perform without <blank /> in his dressing room.</card>
<card>As aprt of his daily regimen, Anderson Cooper sets aside 15 minutes for <blank />.</card>
<card>Turns out that <blank />-Man was neither the hero we needed nor wanted.</card>
<card>Listen, son. If you want to get involved with <blank />, I won't stop you. Just steer clear of <blank />.</card>
<card><blank />. Awesome in theory, kind of a mess in practice.</card>
<card>In the seventh circle of Hell, sinners must endure <blank /> for all eternity.</card>
<card>When you get right down to it, <blank /> is just <blank />.</card>
<card>The blind date was going horrible until we discovered our shared interest in <blank />.</card>
<card>My gym teacher got fired for adding <blank /> to the obstacle course.</card>
</deck>
