<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!--
   Cards Against Humanity black card list, from the fourth expansion.

   Derived from work copyright by Cards Against Humanity LLC,
   Licensed under Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 2.0
   Generic (CC BY-NC-SA 2.0)
-->
<deck name="4rdexp" woeid="23424977" version="1.0">
<card>What's fun until it gets weird?</card>
<card>In the beginning, there was <blank />. And the Lord said, &ldquo;Let there be <blank />.&rdquo;</card>
<card>Wes Anderson's new film tells the story of a precocious child coming to terms with <blank />.</card>
<card><blank /> will never be the same after <blank />.</card>
<card>I'm sorry, sir, but we don't allow <blank /> at the country club.</card>
<card>How am I compensating for my tiny penis?</card>
<card>You've seen the bearded lady! You've seen the ring of fire! Now, ladies and gentlemen, feast your eyes upon <blank />!</card>
<card>We never did find <blank />, but along the way we sure learned a lot about <blank />.</card>
<card>She's up all night for good fun. I'm up all night for <blank />.</card>
<card><blank /> may pass, but <blank /> will last forever.</card>
<card>Dear Leader Kim Jong-un, our village praises your infinite wistom with a humble offering of <blank />.</card>
<card>Man, this is bullshit. Fuck <blank />.</card>
<card>You guys, I saw this crazy movie last night. It opens on <blank />, and then there's some stuff about <blank />, and then it ends with <blank />.</card>
<card>In return for my soul, the Devil promised me <blank />, but all I got was <blank />.</card>
<card>The Japanses have developed a smaller, more efficient version of <blank />.</card>
<card>Alright, bros. Our frat house is condemned, and all the hot slampieces are over at Gamma Phi. The time has come to commence Operation <blank />.</card>
<card>This is the prime of my life. I'm young, hot, and full of <blank />.</card>
<card>I'm pretty sure I'm high right now, because I'm absolutely mesmerized by <blank />.</card>
<card>It lurks in the night. It hungers for flesh. This summer, no one is safe from <blank />.</card>
<card>If you can't handle <blank />, you'd better stay away from <blank />.</card>
<card>Forget everything you know about <blank />, because now we've supercharged it with <blank />.</card>
<card>Honey, I have a new role-play I want to try tonight! You can be <blank />, and I'll be <blank />.</card>
<card>This year's hottest album is &ldquo;<blank />&rdquo; by <blank />.</card>
<card>Every step towards <blank /> gets me a little bit closer to <blank />.</card>
<card>Oprah's book of the month is &ldquo;<blank /> For <blank />: A Story of Hope.&rdquo;</card>
<card>Do <em>not</em> fuck with me! I am literally <blank /> right now.</card>
<card>2 AM in the city that never sleeps. The door swings open and <em>she</em> walks in, lets up to here. Something in her eyes tells me she's looking for <blank />.</card>
<card>As king, how will I keep the peasants in line?</card>
<card>Adventure.<br />Romance.<br /><blank />.<br /><br />From Paramount Pictures, &ldquo;<blank />.&rdquo;</card>
<card>I am become <blank />, destroyer of <blank />!</card>
</deck>
