<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!--
   Cards Against Humanity black card list, from the base (US) set.

   Derived from work copyright by Cards Against Humanity LLC,
   Licensed under Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 2.0
   Generic (CC BY-NC-SA 2.0)
-->
<deck name="base" woeid="23424977" version="1.4">
<card>How did I lose my virginity?</card>
<card>Why can't I sleep at night?</card>
<card>What's that smell?</card>
<card>I got 99 problems but <blank /> ain't one.</card>
<card>Maybe she's born with it. Maybe it's <blank />.</card>
<card>What's the next Happy Meal&reg; toy?</card>
<card>Here is the church<br />Here is the steeple<br />Open the doors<br />And there is <blank /></card>
<card>It's a pity that kids these days are all getting involved with <blank />.</card>
<card>During his childhood, Salvador Dal&iacute; produced hundreds of paintings of <blank />.</card>
<card>Alternative medicine is now embracing the curative powers of <blank />.</card>
<card>And the Academy Award for <blank /> goes to <blank />.</card>
<card>What's that sound?</card>
<card>What ended my last relationship?</card>
<card>MTV's new reality show features eight washed-up celebrities living with <blank />.</card>
<card>I drink to forget <blank />.</card>
<card>I'm sorry, Professor, but I couldn't complete my homework because of <blank />.</card>
<card>What is Batman's guilty pleasure?</card>
<card>This is the way the world ends \ This is the way the world ends \ Not with a bang but with <blank />.</card>
<card>What's a girl's best friend?</card>
<card>TSA guidelines now prohibit <blank /> on airplanes.</card>
<card><blank />. That's how I want to die.</card>
<card>For my next trick, I will pull <blank /> out of <blank />.</card>
<card>In the new Disney Channel Original Movie, Hannah Montana struggles with <blank /> for the first time.</card>
<card><blank /> is a slippery slope that leads to <blank />.</card>
<card>What does Dick Cheney prefer?</card>
<card>Dear Abby,<br />I'm having some trouble with <blank /> and would like your advice.</card>
<card>Instead of coal, Santa now gives the bad children <blank />.</card>
<card>What's the most emo?</card>
<card>In 1,000 years, when paper money is but a distant memory, <blank /> will be our currency.</card>
<card pick="2">What's the next superhero/sidekick duo?</card>
<card>In M. Night Shyamalan's new movie, Bruce Willis discovers that <blank /> had really been <blank /> all along.</card>
<card>A romantic, candlelit dinner would be incomplete without <blank />.</card>
<card><blank />. Betcha can't have just one!</card>
<card>White people like <blank />.</card>
<card><blank />. High five, bro.</card>
<card>Next from J.K. Rowling: Harry Potter and the Chamber of <blank />.</card>
<card>BILLY MAYS HERE FOR <blank />!</card>
<card>In a world ravaged by <blank />, our only solace is <blank />.</card>
<card>War!<br /><br />What is it good for?</card>
<card>During sex, I like to think about <blank />.</card>
<card>What are my parents hiding from me?</card>
<card>What will always get you laid?</card>
<card woeid="2442047">In L.A. County Jail, word is you can trade 200 cigarettes for <blank />.</card>
<card woeid="23424900">What did I bring back from Mexico?</card>
<card>What don't you want to find in your Kung Pao chicken?</card>
<card>What will I bring back in time to convince people that I am a powerful wizard?</card>
<card>How am I maintaining my relationship status?</card>
<card><blank />. It's a trap!</card>
<card>Coming to Broadway this season, <blank />: The Musical.</card>
<card>While the United States raced the Soviet Union to the moon, the Mexican government funneled millions of pesos into research on <blank />.</card>
<card>After the earthquake, Sean Penn brought <blank /> to the people of Haiti.</card>
<card>Next on ESPN2: The World Series of <blank />.</card>
<card>Step 1: <blank />.<br />Step 2: <blank />.<br />Step 3: Profit.</card>
<card>Rumor has it that Vladimir Putin's favorite dish is <blank /> stuffed with <blank />.</card>
<card>But before I kill you, Mr. Bond, I must show you <blank />.</card>
<card>What gives me uncontrollable gas?</card>
<card>What do old people smell like?</card>
<card>The class field trip was completely ruined by <blank />.</card>
<card>When Pharaoh remained unmoved, Moses called down a Plague of <blank />.</card>
<card>What's my secret power?</card>
<card>What's there a ton of in heaven?</card>
<card>What would grandma find disturbing, yet oddly charming?</card>
<card>I never truly understood <blank /> until I encountered <blank />.</card>
<card>What did the U.S. airdrop to the children of Afghanistan?</card>
<card>What helps Obama unwind?</card>
<card>What did Vin Diesel eat for dinner?</card>
<card><blank />: good to the last drop.</card>
<card>Why am I sticky?</card>
<card>What gets better with age?</card>
<card><blank />: kid-tested, mother-approved.</card>
<card>Daddy, why is mommy crying?</card>
<card>What's Teach for America using to inspire inner city students to succeed?</card>
<card>Studies show that lab rats navigate mazes 50% faster after being exposed to <blank />.</card>
<card>Life for American Indians was forever changed when the White Man introduced them to <blank />.</card>
<card>I do not know with what weapons World War III will be fought, but World War IV will be fought with <blank />.</card>
<card>Why do I hurt all over?</card>
<card>What am I giving up for Lent?</card>
<card>In Michael Jackson's final moments, he thought about <blank />.</card>
<card>The Smithsonian Museum of Natural History has just opened an interactive exhibit on <blank />.</card>
<card>When I am President of the United States, I will create the Department of <blank />.</card>
<card>Lifetime&reg; presents <blank />, the story of <blank />.</card>
<card>When I am a billionaire, I shall erect a 50-foot statue to commemorate <blank />.</card>
<card>When I was tripping on acid, <blank /> turned into <blank />.</card>
<card>That's right, I killed <blank />. How, you ask? <blank />.</card>
<card>What's my anti-drug?</card>
<card><blank /> + <blank /> = <blank />.</card>
<card>What never fails to liven up the party?</card>
<card>What's the new fad diet?</card>
<card>Major League Baseball has banned <blank /> for giving players an unfair advantage.</card>
</deck>
